# Mustafa Bozkaya

Gaziantep, Turkey

mustafaegebozkaya555@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mustafa-bozkaya

# **Summary**

Areas of interests:

- -Robotics
- -Artificial intelligence
- -Deep Learning
- -Computer Vision
- -Machine learning
- -Optimization

I allways have been a Researcher, ambitious person. I have been infusing myself with different educations. BECAUSE IT'S WHAT YOU SEE IN ADVANCE OF THE FUTURE CHANGE AND GET READY FOR IT. https://mustafabozkaya.github.io

https://www.kaggle.com/mustafabozka/code

# **Experience**



# Ratificial intelligence R&D Enginer

#### EPİK ROBOTİK

May 2022 - Present (8 months +)

We are working on topics such as Natural navigation solutions, autonomous mobile vehicles, simultaneous location and mapping, machine learning, deep learning, computer vision algorithms

### kaggle Notebooks Contributer

#### Kaggle

Jan 2020 - Present (3 years +)

I have been working in the fields of Machine Learning data Science and deep learning for the last four years. For the past two years, I've been learning in field of Robotics and doing various studies on technologies like react vue js ROS noetic, Ros2, with Python

# Artificial intelligence R&D Engineer

**BOYAR KIMYA AS** 

Mar 2021 - May 2022 (1 year 3 months)

### Project Management Engineer

**Bizce** 

Nov 2019 - Sep 2020 (11 months)

# **Senior Web Developer**

Freelancer.com

Feb 2014 - Apr 2020 (6 years 3 months)

I have done Web applications with html, css, javascript, bootstrap, php with codelgineter laravel, mysql to many companies remotely.

## **Education**

Istanbul University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Industrial Engineering Jan 2014 - Sep 2018

Istanbul University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineer Jun 2011 - Jan 2014

#### özel idare anadolu lisesi

sayısal bölüm 2006 - 2010

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

Introduction to Deep Learning - Global AI Hub

eyJ1c2VyLWlkljoxMDkzOCwiY291cnNlLWlkljoxMTUyMTksImNlcnQtaWQiOilxMTUzODgifQ==

- Intermadiate Machine Learning with Python Global AI Hub
  eyJ1c2VyLWlkljoxMDkzOCwiY291cnNlLWlkljoxMTI4NjQslmNlcnQtaWQiOilxMTMyNjMifQ==
- **DATA VISUALIZATION** Global AI Hub
  eyJ1c2VyLWlkljoxMDkzOCwiY291cnNlLWlkljo4ODc5MiwiY2VydC1pZCl6ljk1Njgyln0=
- Version Control Systems ve Portfolio Global Al Hub
  eyJ1c2VyLWlkljoxMDkzOCwiY291cnNlLWlkljo4ODc5MywiY2VydC1pZCl6ljEwNjkyNSJ9
- Machine Learning with Python Global AI Hub
  eyJ1c2VyLWlkljoxMDkzOCwiY291cnNlLWlkljo3NjU4NSwiY2VydC1pZCl6ljc2ODM4In0=
- Introduction to AI, Robotics and Data Global AI Hub
  eyJ1c2VyLWlkljoxMDkzOCwiY291cnNlLWlkljo2MDg1MCwiY2VydC1pZCl6ljczMDUxln0=
- Data Manipulation Global AI Hub

  eyJ1c2VyLWlkljoxMDkzOCwiY291cnNlLWlkljoxMTEzODcsImNlcnQtaWQiOilxMTEzODkifQ==
- Python For Machine Learnings Simplilearn

- Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Text Mining Simplilearn https://simpli.app.link/kGuKB7zSAub
- Apache Spark Course Simplilearn https://simpli-web.app.link/e/kz9jOCEhDub
- Problem Solving (intermadiate) with Python HackerRank C9EEC51BC2FD
- Certificate of completion Git and GitHub 365 Data Science CC-F580514326
- Certificate of completion Introduction to Jupyter 365 Data Science CC-413D8715B2
- **5 Week Deep Learning Bootcamp** Al Planet formerly DPhi 619541c0-07d9-45cc-820f-582cb4610cd2

## **Skills**

Image Processing • TensorFlow • Deep Learning • Software Design • Linux • Git • Robotics • Web Development • Machine Learning • Robot Operating System (ROS)